Lying down in a helpless state, this man is
suffering from a permanent erection.
It is a physical condition that has
gone beyond his natural control.
So his parents have brought him to
the Synagogue Church of All Nations,
seeking a divine solution. Let's hear from them.
His manhood has been erect for the past 11 days now. It cannot come down.
Ok, stand up, my friend.
T.B. Joshua instructs the man to stand up for an encounter with the Holy Spirit.
With the finger of God, the Prophet prays
for him in the powerful name of Jesus Christ,
expelling all the shades of darkness that have caused his manhood to be permanently erect.
The Word of God is the tool in the hands of the Holy Spirit,
to heal you as it says in Isaiah 53:5,
"By His stripes, we are healed".
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You are free!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
My son is healed. Thank You, Jesus!
After receiving healing in the name of Jesus Christ,
Mr Jude Alobo came back to the
Synagogue Church of All Nations
to testify that the permanent erection has gone,
and his manhood is now back to normal.
Before and After
Free from pain and tension, Mr Jude
gladly shows that his manhood is normal once again.
Hallelujah!
Glory be to God!
Brother, I want you to tap your body.
Tap it with your hands. Press it. How do you feel?
I feel very good now, very fine.
Very normal now. I'm good.
Were you able to touch your private part like this before?
No, I wasn't able to do that because I was in severe pain.
The erection wouldn't let me urinate.
Right now you're touching it. What do you have to say?
I give glory to God, I give thanks to God.
Touch it once again.
You mean the pain is gone?
The pain is gone totally.
To the glory of God, we can see the brother
who suffered from permanent erection,
he couldn't pass urine then without pain.
Every time he wanted to pass urine,
he was always experiencing terrible pain.
But right now we can see him passing urine without any pain, to the glory of God.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Jude Alobo.
Beside me are my mom and my dad.
I am a graduate. I'm from Benue State.
I studied building engineering at the University of Jos.
I came here because I had a permanent erection, asthma, depression and schizophrenia.
The problem started while I was in the university.
I was combining music and studies together,
but the music wasn't forthcoming.
And I wasn't performing well in my studies
so that led me into a depression.
I started taking drugs - marijuana and
other drugs - and having casual sex with prostitutes.
But those drugs didn't work. Instead, they led me into illness.
I was taken to the hospital and I was
diagnosed with depression and schizophrenia.
I was prescribed drugs which I was taking
but those drugs had strong side effects
which was causing me permanent
erection that would last for four hours.
So I decided to stop taking the drugs.
When I went back to the hospital
for my regular check-up,
the doctor gave me an injection - a
combination of all the drugs I was taking
which gave me a permanent
erection that lasted for two months.
They took me to different hospitals,
different churches but the erection didn't go down.
I was in severe pain, I was in serious pain;
I couldn't stand straight, I couldn't sit
down.
I had to lie down because the pain was so serious.
The doctor suggested I should go for an operation
which I refused because it was a 50/50 chance.
So I decided to come to the Synagogue Church of All Nations because I had seen so many people
with the same situation of permanent erection being healed here.
When I came here, the man of God prayed for me and I became healed.
The erection started going down
gradually and the pain started subsiding
and that was how I became okay.
Mr Jude Alobo & Family
Healing Testimony
My word of advice to everyone
out there is to believe in God,
to trust in God - God is the only Healer.
Mr Jude Alobo & Family
Healing Testimony
People of God, Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Arubi Alobo,
just like I've been introduced.
The reason we are here today is to give testimony
regarding the permanent erection of Jude Alobo.
He has said it all.
What I want to add is that the pain he felt -
if you were there, it was like you could feel it as well.
And so I described that pain as the father of all pains
because as he was writhing in pains,
indeed all of us were always crying.
But today, we have come back here to
tell the whole world that God is here.
That whatever problem you have,
that this is the only place
where you can come and receive healing.
I remember, while the pain was on,
we had to visit one hospital or the other.
We went to a particular doctor and
we told him about our condition.
He said we should try another doctor, that he could not handle it.
We went to a second doctor
and he referred us to a hospital
where there are professionals
that could handle such a case.
When we went there, they said that
we should go back to the hospital
where the whole thing started
and when we went to that very hospital,
the doctors said he would go through an operation -
an operation of which they said that it would be 50/50.
As he was not ready to go through such a thing, from there we drove straight to this place.
Right from the hospital, we came over to this place and here he received his healing.
And today he is well.
People of God, praise the Lord!
Hallelujah!
My advice to the whole world is that
we should always listen to the voice of the Lord.
The voice of the Lord may not
be very clear to us at times,
but we have to be very careful to
be able to discern when God is talking to us
so that we will follow the right path.
Testimony Time
My name is Alobo Roselyn.
When it started, we were all confused.
As a mother, the pain that your
son or daughter is going through -
you know that it touches a mother.
I cannot even count the tears I shed.
But I said, "God, you are there".
I have been watching Emmanuel TV for years now.
I said, "What He is doing for others,
He is going to do for me.
I'm not going to allow my son
to enter the theater for the operation.
I'm coming down here for his healing".
And my son, with his own belief, said that he will never enter the theater,
that he's coming down here, that God of T.B. Joshua will do it for him.
With his own belief and the trust we had in God,
we entered a vehicle from
Jos and came down to the arena of liberty.
I was happy when I entered the arena of liberty.
I said, "Yes, my God will do it for me now".
Immediately the man of God touched
my son, the pain was released.
He could not sit down, he could not lie
down. Even to lie down was a problem.
As a mother, I was crying all the time.
So the whole thing just came down.
I thank God, I glorify His name!
Amen.
To God be the glory.
The advice I have for people all
over the world as a mother:
If your son is going through pain,
just have patience and trust in God.
Call on God and He is going to rescue you from that pain.
TT: Lizz Ndungu 04/08/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 08/08/2018